These delusions are contagious
The Little Stranger is a mystery, horror film directed by Lenny Abrahamson.
In a dusty post-war summer in rural Warwickshire, a doctor is
called to a patient at lonely Hundreds Hall.
Home to the Ayres family for over two centuries, the
Georgian house is now in decline.
But are the Ayreses haunted by something more sinister than a dying way of life?
Dr. Faraday, played by Domhnall Gleeson.
Caroline Ayres, played by Ruth Wilson.
Roderick Ayres, played by Will Poulter.
Young Faraday, played by Oliver Zetterström.
Mrs. Ayres, played by Charlotte Rampling.
Betty, played by Liv Hill.
The Little Stranger is a 2018 gothic drama film directed by Lenny Abrahamson and written by
Lucinda Coxon, based on the 2009 novel of the same name by Sarah Waters.
The film stars Domhnall Gleeson, Ruth Wilson, Will
Poulter and Charlotte Rampling.
Set in 1948, the plot follows a doctor who visits an old house where his
mother used to work, only to discover it may hold a dark secret.
The film was released in the United Kingdom on 21 September 2018 and in the United States on
31 August 2018 by Focus Features, receiving positive reviews from critics.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.